<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>ghost shop</name>
    <directory>ghost shop</directory>
    <id>2777572191</id>
    <description>Disclaimer: this is a beta version and will be deleted once the full mod is published. Do not award it, please ._.
Also you gotta play at least one run to make it work properly

A new mechinc for the Mirror floor

It contains currently 5 shop layouts which will vary in it's content depending on the items you had in your last run.

Layouts:
- 1 rare lucky layout (6 items/ &quot;better&quot; items/100% haunted chest)
- 3 normal layouts (5 items/50% haunted chest)
- 1 rare bad layout (4 items)

Item cost:
- Quality 0 -2: 15¢
- Quality 3: 15-20¢
- Quality 4: 15-25¢

How does it work?
- Each layout has a total number of items (let's call them slots) it can contain.

- if you win the game or die, then the items you have will be saved (depending on their item quality) in five tables.

- Each slot in the shop gets assigned a quality. This indicates the max quality which it can spawn.
If it can't spawn an item of this quality, because you didn't have more items of this quality, then the quality of the slot will decrease by 1.
If no item can be spawned, then a shop sign will be spawned.

- The item quality which can be assigned to a slot can be increased by completing floors or killing an end boss. Tho beating one will trade this with the bonus you can get from completing floors.

- 1 slot is always at max quality. So as long as you had atleast one item and this item isn't a story item you can always find 1 item in the shop.

- you gotta choose between this shop and the normal shop on the floor. One exists and one is just an empty reflection.

To do list:
- steam thumbnail
- steam images
- finish Unique Spikes

post poned:

- coop ghosts (mod compatibility)
- modded item support. If duable
- Andromeda. If duable</description>
    <version>1.10</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
</metadata>
